ILGWU Western States Region Records 5780/115
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- American Thermo Seal, Incorporated [folder 6 of 6], 1982 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Anaku Quilting Company, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Anjac Fashions, 1976-1978 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Anna Myers Sportswear, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Annetta of California, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Antaky Quilting Company, 1973-1978 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Arrow Belt of California, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Aspen Skiwear, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Armak and Company [folder 1 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Armak and Company [folder 1 of 3], 1979 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Armak and Company [folder 2 of 3], 1979 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Armak and Company [folder 3 of 3], 1979 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  Spanish
- Armak and Company, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Armak and Company [folder 2 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- American Thermo Seal, Company, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Annetta of California, 1976-1979 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Balboa Swimwear Company, Incorporated, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Balboa Swimwear Company, Incorporated [folder 1 of 2], 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Balboa Swimwear Company, Incorporated [folder 1 of 4], 1981 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Balboa Swimwear Company, Incorporated, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Balboa Swimwear Company, Incorporated [folder 2 of 4], 1981 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Balboa Swimwear Company, Incorporated: Medical Insurance, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Balboa Swimwear Company, Incorporated [folder 3 of 4], 1981 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Balboa Swimwear Company, Incorporated [folder 4 of 4], 1981 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Balboa Swimwear Company, Incorporated [folder 2 of 2], 1982 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Ray C. Bannon dba Sav-A-Day Linen Service, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Ray C. Bannon dba Sav-A-Day Linen Service, 1981-1983 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Barbizon of Utah, 1974-1980 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Barbizon of Utah, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Bedspreads of California, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Bar-Jo's Sportswear, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Beam Corporation dba Toleson Industries, Incorporated [folder 1 of 2], 1980 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Beam Corporation dba Toleson Industries, Incorporated [folder 2 of 2], 1980 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Belair Belt Company, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Birdwell Enterprises, Incorporated, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Birdwell Enterprises, Incorporated, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Birdwell Enterprises, Incorporated v. Local 512, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Blue Cross: Stop (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Bouquet Fashions, 1976-1978 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Bronson of California, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Bullock's, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- California Braid, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- California Fashions, Incorporated, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- California Sample Service Company, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- California Sample Service Company [folder 1 of 3], 1980 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- California Sample Service Company [folder 2 of 3], 1980 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- California Sample Service Company [folder 1 of 2], 1982 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- California Sample Service Company [folder 2 of 2], 1982 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- California Schiffli, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Cappi Originals, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 34)
- Carol Lee Fashions, 1971-1978 (Box 19, Folder 35)
- Carter Precision Parts Exchange, Incorporated, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 36)
- Cast Metal Finishing, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 37)
- California Bias Binding, 1973-1977 (Box 19, Folder 38)
- California Sample Service Company, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 39)
- California Sample Service Company [folder 3 of 3], 1980 (Box 19, Folder 40)
- Accountants: Wolf and Schulman, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Adopt a Farah Family, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- ALF-CIO, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Alioto for Governor, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Avis: Accident Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Avis: Accident Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Bernstein, Theodore: Counsel, 1970-1972 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Board of Trustees: Minutes, 1970-1973 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- California Labor Council on Political Education, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- California Labor Federation, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Chaiken, Sol C., 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Daniels, Wilbur: Executive Vice President, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- D. and B. Reports, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Delinquent and Quarterly Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- California Department of Industrial Relations, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Donations Forms, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Local 512: Election and Objection Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Local 482: Election and Objection Committee, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Local 452: Election and Objection Committee, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Local 84: Election and Objection Committee, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Local 96: Election and Objection Committee, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Local 55: Election and Objection Committee, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- L.A. Joint Board: Election and Objection Committee, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Arnold, Evelyn, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- ILGWU L.A. Joint Board: Election Procedures, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Employer Contributions: All Funds, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Fair Trade Practices Department, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Filipino Bayanihan, Incorporated, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Finance Department: New York, 1971-1974 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- L.A. Joint Baord: Financial Report, 1964-1973 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Financial Reports: Health Center, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- L.A. Designers Retirement Fund: Financial Statements, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Financial Reports: Vacation Health and Welfare Fund, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- WSR Monthly Financial Reports, 1970-1973 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Financial Reports: San Francisco Joint Board, L.A. Joint Board, Subordinates Accounts, Administrative Fund, WSR, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- Frontlash, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 36)
- Garment Contractors Association of Southern California, Incorporated, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 37)
- ILGWU: Golden Club Los Angeles, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 38)
- Grossman, Maurice M., 1970-1972 (Box 20, Folder 39)
- Histadrut, 1970-1973 (Box 20, Folder 40)
- ILGWU Convention, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 41)
- ILGWU Convention, 1959-1965 (Box 20, Folder 42)
- ILGWU: Other Locals, Departments, Joint Boards, etc., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 43)
- Label Distribution, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 44)
- League for Industrial Democracy, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 45)
- Legislative Department, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 46)
- Levin, Douglas: Vice President, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 47)
- Levin, Meyer: New York, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 48)
- Leviton, Philip: Copies of Letters, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 49)
- Lindsay, Gilbert W., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 50)
- Lipsig, James: Assistant Executive Secretary, 1970-1973 (Box 20, Folder 51)
- Lokiec, Mitchell: Management Engineering, 1964-1972 (Box 20, Folder 52)
- Los Angeles County COPE, 1970-1972 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Los Angeles County Federation, 1971-1975 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- L.A. Union Label Council, 1969-1971 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Memos, 1971-1973 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- National Labor Relations Board, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- National Labor Relations Board, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Negotiations, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Negotiations: Danica Clothing Company, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Negotiations: L.A. Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Negotiations: Independent Manufacturers and Jobbers, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Negotiations: L.A. Coat and Suit Contractors, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Negotiations: Designers Agreement, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- News Clippings, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- News Release: Justice, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Smith, Ralph: Organization Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Phoenix Office, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Political and Education, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Transportation Department: Wolmer, Helen and Lipsig, J., 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Regional Planning Commission: Zoning Ordinance, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Rolnick, Louis: National Retirement Fund, 1964-1973 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Rolnick, Louis: National Retirement Fund, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Rolnick, Louis: Welfare and Health Benefits, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Shop Averages, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Staff Meeting: Notices, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Scholarship, Training, Education, Political, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Strike Reports and Expenses, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Union Label Department (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Unruh, Jess, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Teper, Lazare: Strike Repots 1973 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- 1973 Strike Sanction Requests (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Stulberg, Louis: Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Teper, Lazare: Research Department, Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Teper, Lazare: Research Department, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 34)
- Teper, Lazare: Research Department, New Plants Notices, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 35)
- Tyler, Gus: Assistant President, 1969-1973 (Box 21, Folder 36)
- Thank You Notes, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 37)
- United States Department of Labor, 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 38)
- Vacation Health Death and Welfare Fund: Assessment, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 39)
- Wall, Cornelius: Correspondence to President Stuberg, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 40)
- Wall, Cornelius: Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 41)
- Wall, Cornelius: Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 42)
- Wall, Cornelius: Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 21, Folder 43)
- Western States Region, 1971-1973 (Box 21, Folder 44)
- ILGWU Supplementary Unemployment Benefit Fund: Rules and Regulations, 1965-1976 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- ILGWU: Campaign Committee, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Campaign Contribution Lists, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Berner, Peter: ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee: Western States Region [folder 1 of 2] (Box 22, Folder 5)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee: Western States Region [folder 2 of 2] (Box 22, Folder 6)
- National Labor Relations Board: Rules and Regulations, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- ILGWU: Western States Region Election Procedures and Materials [folder 1 of 3], 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- ILGWU: Western States Region Election Procedures and Materials [folder 2 of 3], 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- ILGWU: Western States Region Election Procedures and Materials [folder 3 of 3], 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Catalina Manufacturing Plant, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Catalina: Letter Threat, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Cherrybelle Manufacturing Company, Incorporated, 1975-1978 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Chesney of Hollywood, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Chic Lingerie Company, Incorporated, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Closed Matters, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Century Pattern Company, Incorporated, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Coleman Company, Incorporated, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Collegiate Pacific Company, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Cotemporary Creations, Incorporated, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Contessa of California, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Copeland and Company, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- D&M Fashions, 1975-1978 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- D&M Fashions, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- D&M Fashions, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- D'Andre, Incorporated, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Deanna Dee, 1961-1978 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- D'Mia Fashions, Incorporated, 1982-1985 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- D'Mia Fashions, Incorporated [folder 1 of 3], 1983 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- D'Mia Fashions, Incorporated [folder 2 of 3], 1983 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- D'Mia Fashions, Incorporated, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- D'Mia Fashions, Incorporated [folder 3 of 3], 1983 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- D'Roma Coats, Incorporated, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Daisy of California, Incorporated, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Ditto Apparel of California, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Domino of California, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Dumas of California, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Dumas and Canez, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Domenico Manufacturers, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Eddy Moss, Incorporated, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- E+E, Incorporated, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- El Jo Negotiations, 1979-1981 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- El Jo Styles, 1972-1978 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- El Jo Styles, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- El Jo Styles, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- El Jo Styles, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Emgee Marvel Embroidery Company, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- Electro-Winders Company, Incorporated, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 38)
- Electro-Winders Company, Incorporated, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 39)
- Emphasis of California, 1967-1980 (Box 23, Folder 40)
- Miss Elliette, Incorporated, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 41)
- Emphasis of California, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 42)
- Employment Development Department [folder 1 of 5], 1977-1980 (Box 23, Folder 43)
- Employment Development Department [folder 2 of 5], 1977-1980 (Box 23, Folder 44)
- Employment Development Department [folder 3 of 5], 1977-1980 (Box 23, Folder 45)
- Employment Development Department [folder 4 of 5], 1977-1980 (Box 23, Folder 46)
- Employment Development Department [folder 5 of 5], 1977-1980 (Box 23, Folder 47)
- D'Mia Fashion, Joli'D Coats, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 48)
- Fashion Time, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Fieldcraft, Incorporated, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Fritzi of California, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Funky, Incorporated, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Fels Company, 1974-1978 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Monique Sportswear, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Fisher Dress Manufacturing Company, 1974-1978 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Fran Lee of California, 1974-1978 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Fun Striders, Incorporated, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Funky, Incorporated, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Funky, Incorporated: Local 512, 1979-1981 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- A. Garfunkel, Incorporated, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Garment Corporation of America, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Gasser/Olds Company, Incorporated, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- General Knit Corporation, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Gino Tailors, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Greencastle, Limited, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Greencastle, Incorporated, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- E.L. Gruber Underwear Company, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- H&M Sportswear, 1971-1978 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Hae Joon Oh, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Hartfield-Zodys, Incorporated, 1974-1977 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Hazel Cid, Incorporated, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Hedman Hedders, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Hedman Hedders, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Helga, Incorporated, 1974-1978 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Hollywood Bed and Spring, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Hudon Apparel, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Ideal Pleating and Stitching, 1974-1978 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- ILGWU: Barbara, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- In time of California, Incorporated, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- In time of California, Incorporated, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- J-Z Contracting Company, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- J-Z Contracting Company, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 34)
- Jaylyn Fashions, Incorporated, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- Jenelle of California, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Jet Set, Incorporated, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 37)
- Jodi Hill: California Mates, Incorporated, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 38)
- Helga, Incorporated, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 39)
- Helga, Incorporated, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 40)
- Jody Tootique, 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Johnson: Jolie Belts Company, 1981-1984 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Jolene Company, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Jolie Belts Company, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Jolie Belts Company: Copies File, 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Jolei Belts Company: Subpoena, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Jolie Belts Company, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Jolie Belts Company, 1956-1975 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Jolie Belts Company, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Jolie Belts Company, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Jolie Belts Company: NLRB Hearing, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Joli'D Coats, Incorporated, 1979-1984 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Joli'D Coats, Incorporated, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Joli'D Coats, Incorporated, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- K-Mart: Teamsters Raid (Box 25, Folder 15)
- K-Mart Apparel Corporation, 1971-1978 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Charles Sportswear Manufacturing Company, 1979-1981 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Karl's Shoe Stores, Limited, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Kathi Din Manufacturing, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Robert Kaufman and Company, Incorporated, 1971-1978 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Kellwood Company, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Knits International, 1975-1980 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Kooki Jar, Incorporated, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Koret of California, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- L.A. Knitting Mills, Incorporated, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- L.A. Knitting Mills, Incorporated, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- L.C. Mae of Hollywood, Incorporated, 1971-1978 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Lealou Emblems, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Lebeau Emblem Company, Incorporated: Veronica, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Lebeau Emblem Company, Incorporated, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Lebeau Emblem Company, Incorporated, 1981-1983 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Lebeau Emblem Company, Incorporated (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Louis Krieger Company, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Lebanon of California, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Lermer Packaging Company, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Levi Strauss Company, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Levi Strauss Company, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Levi Strauss Company, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Lilli Diamond of California, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Local 482: Southern California Davis Pleating, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Local 512: Motif, Incorporated, 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Contractors Association, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Los Angeles Pleating Company, 1974-1977 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Los Angeles Small Pleating Association, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Los Angeles Small Pleating Association, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Loubella Extendables, Incorporated, 1975-1980 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Loubella Extendables, Incorporated, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Lou-Gene of California, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Mahler Sales Company, Incorporated, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- M&J Manufacturing, Incorporated, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Main on Foods Corporation: Employee Approval of ULP Settlement, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Main on Foods Corporation, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Main on Foods Corporation: Employee Approval of ULP Settlement, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Main on Foods Corporation, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Main on Foods Corporation: Affidavit (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Main on Foods Corporation, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Manny Industries, Incorporated, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Manny Industries, Incorporated, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Manny Industries, Incorporated: Max Rawicz Closure, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- ILGWU Local 512: Main on Foods Corporation, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- ILGWU Local 512: Southern California Davis Pleating Company, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- ILGWU Local 482: Stual Manufacturing Company, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- ILGWU Local 512: American Thermo-Seal, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- Wolf, Max B: Political and Education [folder 1 of 2], 1969-1973 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Wolf, Max B: Political and Education [folder 2 of 2], 1969-1973 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Wolf, Max B: Political and Education [folder 1 of 3], 1971-1975 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Wolf, Max B: Political and Education [folder 2 of 3], 1971-1975 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Wolf, Max B: Political and Education [folder 3 of 3], 1971-1975 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Western States Region, 1971-1974 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Wolf, Max B: Political and Education, Newspaper Clippings, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- King, Georgia: Holly Stores, Incorporated, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Unemployment Signup Sheets, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Wolf, Max B: Political and Education, 1971-1974 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Wolf, Max B: Political and Education [folder 1 of 3], 1970-1974 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Wolf, Max B: Political and Education [folder 2 of 3], 1970-1974 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Wolf, Max B: Political and Education [folder 3 of 3], 1970-1974 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Wolf, Max B: Political and Education [folder 1 of 2], 1970-1975 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Wolf, Max B: Political and Education [folder 2 of 2], 1970-1975 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Wolf, Max B: Political and Education [folder 1 of 3], 1971-1973 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Wolf, Max B: Political and Education [folder 2 of 3], 1971-1973 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Wolf, Max B: Political and Education [folder 3 of 3], 1971-1973 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Manny Industries, Incorporated [folder 1 of 3], 1981 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Manny Industries, Incorporated [folder 2 of 3], 1981 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Manny Industries, Incorporated [folder 3 of 3], 1981 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Mary Jane Company, Incorporated, 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Mayfair Coat and Suit Company, 1974-1979 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Meggan, Incorporated, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Meggan, Incorporated, 1977-1980 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Mensics Company, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Messerman Sportswear, Incorporated, 1977-1980 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Metric Products, Incorporated, 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous, 1974-1978 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Moab Sportswear: Negotiations, 1978-1979 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Moab Sportswear, Incorporated, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Moab Sportswear, Incorporated, 1978-1980 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Mode O'Day Company, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Mode O'Day Company, 1976-1978 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Modern Button Company of California [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Modern Button Company of California [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Mona Lee of California [folder 1 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Mona Lee of California [folder 2 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Mona Lee of California [folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Mona Lee of California: J-Z Contracting, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Mona Lee of California [folder 1 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Mona Lee of California [folder 2 of 2], 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Mona Lee of California [folder 2 of 2], 1979 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Moran Drapery, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- Morris Maler Shirt Manufacturing Company, 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- Motif, Incorporated, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- Motif, Incorporated, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- Morris Maler Manufacturing Company, Incorporated, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- Mary Jane Sportswear, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- Motif, Incorporated [folder 1 of 3], 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Motif, Incorporated, 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Motif, Incorporated, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Motif, Incorporated [folder 2 of 3], 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Motif, Incorporated [folder 3 of 3], 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Moya/Park Pleating Company, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Moya/Park Pleating Company, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- MRC Sportswear, Incorporated, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Mister Herbert of California, Incorporated, 1973-1976 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Mister Herbert of California, Incorporated, 1980-1981 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Mr. Pleat, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Mr. Pleat [folder 1 of 2], 1980 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Mr. Pleat: Case Closed, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Mr. Pleat [folder 2 of 2], 1980 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Mr. Pleat: Closed, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Mutual Industries, 1974-1979 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Nit Fit Knitting Mills, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Anjac Fashions, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Nehi Record Distributing Corporation, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Nifty Costume Company, Incorporated, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 20)